Test_id	Module 	Description 	Test_Steps	      Expected result	Actual result 	     Status	         Comments
TC_01 	Audio	Test audio playback functionality 	open the music player and  play audio	audio should play with out any disturbances 	       audio is playing with out any disturbances	     PASS	
TC_02 	Audio	Test pause and resume during playback 	open the music player and  play audio 	Audio should stop when it is paused and play when it resume  	Audio is working according to the input  	     PASS	
TC_03	Audio	Test volume controls	open the music player  play audio, increase or decrease the volume	volume should be controled acordingly to the user input 	Audio is working according to the input  	      PASS	
TC_04	Audio	  Test the audio quality   	open the music player play audio 	Audio should play with out any background noise 	 Audio is playing smoothly	    PASS 	
TC_05	Audio	Test the audio is working on different devices 	play the audio in different devices	Audio should play in all devices	when playing audio it showing cannot play audio	     FAIL	Audio can support any device for playback
TC_06	Audio	Test  the audio is working on different  formats 	1.play the audio in MP3 format. 2.Play the audio in FLAC 3.Play the audio in AAC	1.2.3.Audio should be played ithout any interputions	1.The audio is played without any interpution 2.3.s not played 	     FAIL	wav,AAC   is not supported 
TC_07     	       Audio      	Test audio interaction with output device      	1.open the music player play audio externally,insert the head phones many times and bluetooth many times ,check output is coming according to the user preference 	output should come according to the user preference     	output is working according to the user preference     	    PASS      	
TC_08	        Audio	Test how system notifications affect audio playback	1.open the music player and play music. 2.Recieve the whatapp notification. 	1.Music should be played 2.The music should stop while receiving the notification.and it should be resumed after notification ends.	notifications interupting the audio playback	     FAIL	
TC_08	     Audio	Recording test	1.Open recording application 2.Record the audio in Meeting,AAC,Interview mode 3.Play the recorded files	1.Recorded files must be played without any interpuution.		    PASS      	
TC_09	    Audio	Test battery consumption during continuous audio playback (mobile).for offline music.	open the music player and play audio	Battery consumption should be reasonable and not drain quickly.	Battery life is sustained during long audio playback	     PASS	
TC_10	    Audio	Test multiple audio streams playing simultaneously (e.g., background music and app sound effects)	1.open the music player and play audio 2.play the games	Both audio streams should play without interference or muting 	  audio streams mix correctly.  	       PASS	
TC_11	   Audio	Test echo cancellation during recording.	open the mobile and record the audio	The system should cancel echo and record clear audio. 	Echo is suppressed, and recording quality is clear.	       PASS	
TC_12	   Audio	Test how the system handles incoming calls during audio playback.	1.open the music player and play music 2.Take another mobile and call to your number	Audio should pause during the call and resume after.	Playback pauses during the call and resumes without issues.	       PASS	
TC_13	   Audio	Test audio playback for long-duration files.	open the music player and play long audio	audio should play with out any stopping	Audio is playing continuously for long files 	       PASS	
TC_14	   Audio	Test audio playback for short-duration files.	open the music player and play short audio 	Short audio files should play completely.	Audio is playing completely. 	       PASS	
TC_15	   Audio	Test the audio play back while connecting with bluetooth 	open the mobile connect the bluetooth and play audio	Audio should play when bluetooth is connected and stop when bluetooth is turned off.	Audio is playing with respect to the bluetooth status.	        PASS	
TC_16	 Audio VOIP CALL	Test the audio via whats app 	 Use the built-in music player  1. When playing music outside,chat with Whatsapp voice phone and video call.respectively, adjust the volume, answer and hang up and refuse during the ringing process  2. Come to  Whatsapp voice phone and video call respectively. During the call, enter the built-in player again and click to play music, voice phone switches hands-free and hand-held three times respectively. Hang up the phone 	1.WeChat voice, video phone call ringtone and hanging sound without noise pop sound,Click to answer normally, test machine and the auxiliary machine have clear sound and no echo noise, etc.  Hang up the phone and continue to play music 2. Music can be played, hand-held sound is output from the earpiece, hands-free sound is output from the speaker,test machine music sound cannot be heard by the auxiliary machine during the call, and the call sound is clear. without noise echo.After hanging up the phone, you can continue to play music and output it from the speaker without pop noise.	Audio is playing correctly	        PASS	
TC_17	     Audio	Test the audio on internet call	1.When inserting standard headphones to play music,come to Whatsapp voice and video chat respectively. Adjust the volume, answer hang-up and refuse during the ringing process 2. Come to Whatsapp voice phone and video call under- standard headphones respectively. During the call, enter the built-in player again and click to play music, voice phone switches hands-free and handheld respectively. Headphones 3 times each, hang up the phone  3. Digital headphones come to Whatsapp voice phone and video call respectively.During the call, enter the built-in player again and click to play music. voice phones switch hands-free, handheld and earphones  three times each. Hang up the phone 4. When connecting Bluetooth headset to play music, chat with WeChat volce phone and video phone respectively. Adjust the volume during the ringing process, answer hang-up and refuse.  In the process of answering, enter the built-in player again and click to play music. Switch hand-held.	Expected result: 1. Whatsapp voice, video phone call ringtone and hang- up sound without noise pop sound, click Answer to answer normally, test machine and auxiliary machine call sound is clear, no echo and no pop sound 2.Music can be played, output from headphones by default, and the sound in the call is clear without noise echo. Switch hands-free and output sound from the corresponding speaker and earpiece after holding.  The call sound is clear and there is no noise echo. If you hang up the phone, you can continue to play music output from the speaker, without pop noise. 3. You can play music, output from headphones by default, and the sound in the call is clear without noise echo. After switching hands- free and hand-held, you can output sound from the corresponding speaker and earpiece,  and the call sound is clear without noise echo. Hang up the phone and continue to play music. Output from the speaker, No pop noise.	Audio is playing correctly	       PASS	
TC_18	     Audio	Install the star maker	1.Enter system settings-sound and vibration-earphone listening back.turn on  earphone listening back" switch 2.Connect wire-controlled earphones with MIC, start starmaker application, enter application settings, and turn on the application earphone listening back" switch. Use clear singing and backup singing mode to sing songs, check whether K songs have ear return sound effects 3. Turn off the Headphone Back Listening switch of K songs  application, record songs again, and check whether songs have ear return sound effects. 4.Enter settings,turn off Headphone Back Listening" switch, record songs again,and check whether songs.	Expected result: 1.The switch can be turned on  2. only songs apply ear return sound effects, and there are no abnormal sounds such as pop sounds and noises. 3. K songs have OPPO ear return sound effects  4. K songs have no ear return sound effects                              	Audio is playing correctly	      PASS	
